in a previous tutorial from a few years
在几年前的一个教程中
ago we went over how you can apply
在此之前，我们讨论了如何申请
Vector Textures in inkscape by using
使用Inkscape中的矢量纹理
path operations as it turns out though
尽管如此，路径操作
there is a more efficient way to
有一种更有效的方法来
accomplish this using a relatively new
使用一种相对较新的
feature in inkscape known as inverse
Inkscape中称为反转的功能
masking and I'd like to share that with
蒙面，我想和大家一起分享
you in this tutorial
本教程中的您
so to get us started here the object I
因此，为了让我们从这里开始，对象是
will be working with is this text object
将使用的是此文本对象
here that was previously a text object
这里以前是文本对象
but I converted it to a path now it's
但我把它转换成了一条小路
important to understand that what we're
重要的是要理解我们是什么
going to do in this lesson only works on
本课中要执行的操作仅适用于
objects that are vector pads so if
对象作为向量垫，因此如果
you're working with a text object or a
您正在使用文本对象或
shape that you've drawn with the shape
使用该形状绘制的形状
tool you'll have to convert it to a path
工具，您必须将其转换为路径
first by selecting it and going to path
首先选择它并转到路径
and selecting object to path and once
并选择要路径的对象并一次
you do that you'll be good to go so what
你做到了，你就可以走了，那又怎么样？
I'm going to do now is import my Vector
我现在要做的是导入我的向量
texture I'm going to open my folder and
纹理我要打开我的文件夹并
I'm going to grab the SVG file and just
我要获取SVG文件，然后
click and drag that onto the canvas if
单击并将其拖到画布上，如果
you want to follow along with what I'm
你想跟上我的脚步
doing here I'll put a link in the
执行此操作时，我将在
description to where you can download
可下载的位置的说明
these textures
这些纹理
and once it's imported I'm just going to
一旦它被进口，我就会
scale it down and size it up and
缩小规模，扩大规模，然后
position it where I would like it to be
把它放在我想放的地方
relative to the subject that I'll be
相对于我将会成为的主题
applying it to so I'm going to move this
将其应用于，所以我要移动这个
on top of it like that
最重要的是这样
now normally what we would do is we
通常我们会做的是
would select both of these objects and
会同时选择这两个对象并
do a path difference but the problem
做一个路径差异，但问题是
with using an object like a texture to
使用类似纹理的对象来
do something like that is that this
做这样的事情是这样的
texture consists of thousands of nodes
纹理由数千个节点组成
maybe even tens of thousands of nodes
甚至可能是数以万计的节点
and if you perform path operations with
如果使用以下命令执行路径操作
it it's going to slow down your computer
如果它会让你的电脑变慢
a lot so it's a really inefficient way
很多，所以这是一种非常低效的方式
of doing things instead what we're going
而不是去做我们要做的事情
to do is with both objects selected we
要做的是选择两个对象，我们
will go to object
将转到Object
mask and we're going to choose set
面具，我们将选择Set
inverse mask
反掩码
and once you do that it's going to apply
一旦你这样做了，它就会适用于
the texture to the object as you can see
对象的纹理，如您所见
there and if I zoom in all the way you
在那里，如果我全程放大你
can see that the vector element has been
可以看到向量元素已经被
preserved in fact all of that texture in
实际上保存了所有的质地
there is negative space if I were to
如果我要去，就会有负数空间
grab my rectangle tool and draw a
抓起我的矩形工具，画一个
rectangle and position that beneath
矩形，并将其放置在下面
everything
所有的一切
you can see those negative you can see
你能看到那些你能看到的负片
the black background showing through
穿出的黑色背景
those negative space areas like that
像这样的负空间区域
now if at any point you want to remove
现在，如果您想在任何时候删除
the texture the good thing about this
质地这件事的好处
instead of using path operations is that
与使用路径操作不同的是
it's also non-destructive so you can
它也是非破坏性的，所以你可以
undo this at any point you could just
在任何时候撤消此操作，您只需
select the object and go to object and
选择对象并转到对象，然后
go to mask and choose release mask
转到遮罩并选择释放遮罩
foreign
国外
point you have your preserved text
点您保留的文本
object and the vector texture as it was
对象和原样的矢量纹理
previously so that is a much more
以前，所以这是一个多得多的
efficient way of applying Vector
应用向量的一种有效方法
textures to objects using inkscape if
在以下情况下使用Inkscape为对象添加纹理
you found this lesson useful then
你觉得这一课很有用吗？
consider checking out my inkscape master
考虑一下我的Inkscape大师
class it's a collection of over 60
班级它是一个超过60个人的集合
videos where I go over all of the tools
我浏览了所有工具的视频
and features in inkscape and I explain
和Inkscape中的功能，我解释
what they are and demonstrate how they
它们是什么并演示它们如何
work kind of like how I did in this
就像我在这件事上做的那样
video we even have a private Community
视频我们甚至有一个私人社区
where you can ask questions and get help
在这里您可以提出问题并获得帮助
from me anytime you want and best of all
在你想要的任何时候从我这里，最好的是
there's no monthly membership fees you
你不需要缴纳月费
just pay 17 one time and you're in for
只需一次性支付17英镑，你就会面临
Life I'll have some information about
我会有一些关于生活的信息
that down below if you want to check
如果您想查看下面的内容
that out as always thanks for watching
这是一如既往的感谢收看
thank you
谢谢